hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
It's close.
That's strange.
There hasn't been even
one trap set for a while...
Shikamaru, what do you think?
We're being underestimated.
Those guys think the only one
following them is that big guy.
They don't need to set
a trap on their man.
How dare they underestimate us!
It seems you're right.
We are being
completely underestimated.
However, this is our chance.
Yeah... We'll take them by surprise.
Your Opponent
is me!
That Jirobo is late.
No, he's already here.
Aw c'mon, what took you so long?
Sorry.
It took time to eat the scums' Chakra.
Hey fatso, don't you dare drag!
Hurry up and carry that coffin...
That's your job you vulgar swine.
I know.
What Jirobo...
You're awfully easygoing today.
What do you mean?
I'm just saying I'm not handing you
the coffin.
Because you're not Jirobo!
This time let me do it.
Sakon, Tayuya, you guys go ahead!
Jirobo always corrects
Tayuya's choice of words.
Heh, I see.
Ninja Art: Spider Web Net.
You!
Ninja Art: Spiral Spider Web
Naruto!
Now Kiba, Akamaru!
He shouldn't be able to
move in mid-air.
Fang Over Fang!
I won't let you get away!
That's my line.
Look at your feet.
You!
It's too soon for you to think
you captured us with a thing like this!
Shut up!
C'mon what the hell is
that fatso doing dammit!
It was a mistake to leave
behind the weakest of us after all.
Got it.
— Neji!
— What?!
Me, Naruto, Kiba, and Neji...
Even though we've followed the plan
it's no good.
I'm going to cocoon you.
Damn!
Damn it! Damn it!
What's with this thread?! It won't cut.
It's useless.
My thread is so strong that
even if two elephants pulled away
it wouldn't break.
Shadow Clone... Interesting.
The thread is sticking...
This stickiness is probably made
by mixing Chakra with
his special body fluid.
Moreover this strength. Even after
it's been released from his hands...
Chakra's continuously flowing
in the thread.
It's impossible...
The level of the Jutsu is unrealistic.
Calm down... Just calm down...
my Chakra.
Ninja Art:
Gum Style Spider Thread.
It's a different color than
the thread from before.
What's he gonna do?
It's quickly solidifying, huh...
You are the first one
so it's like a little entertainment.
Now I'll play a game to see
which of you is the real one.
What did you say?!
First is... you at the end.
Naruto!
It was a clone, huh.
Well, this one next!
What a lucky guy.
Next I'll do two at a time.
The odds are 2 to 1.
This guy has great luck
but it's either one or the other now!
Turns out he made it to the last.
Well, it was fun as a game
but now the game's over.
Die!
The first one is done.
What?!
I see the real body made
its shadow clones get caught
and hid himself and
waited for a chance, huh.
For a small fish like that to make
such a plan in those circumstances...
You're not too bad... but...
You're at the end of the line. Die!
What?!
Naruto, your stall was helpful.
Neji!
You... How...?!
Substance with Chakra base...
It's meaningless in front
of Gentle Fist
that destroys by pouring
Chakra through.
That guy's Jutsu...
Evidently I'm the only one
who can fight it.
Go!
I'll take care of this.
What's wrong? Hey Akamaru.
Apparently this guy's stronger
than the fatso before.
Quite a bit stronger.
If we're not prepared for
"one person, one kill"
then it's not going to work out.
That's what you said earlier.
Yeah, that's right.
Plus we won't be able to catch up
with Sasuke if we stall here.
Choji hasn't come back either.
The reason we're doing this
is because of the mission
to bring back Sasuke.
But that's not all.
What we are after and trying
to protect is the bond
of the Shinobi of
the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
Do you remember Iruka's words
at the Third Hokage's funeral?
Iruka-sensei, why do people risk
their lives for others?
When someone dies
they depart with their past,
present, and future.
Many people die on missions
or at war.
And their death is surprisingly
unceremonious... they simply die.
Hayate was one of those people.
Those who die have dreams
and goals too...
But everyone has things that
are equally important.
Parents, siblings, friends, lovers...
Those who are dear to them.
the people important to you.
The connection to the people
you trust and help mutually
the people important to you
from the day you were born.
And the thread that
connects you and your people
gets stronger through time.
It's not a theory.
That's what a person does
as the thread is established
because they're important to you...
Look, Sasuke is heading
towards Orochimaru.
We can't let Orochimaru get
a hold of someone from our village.
Absolutely not.
And...
Naruto...
Your eyes are better than mine.
Right now Sasuke is...
in the darkness.
Hurry up and go!
I'll catch up with you all!
Gotcha!
Okay! Let's go!
You along with Choji
be sure to catch up!
Yeah...
Neji, be absolutely sure to catch up!
Heh... think I'll let them get away?!
Byakugan!
Here it comes!
This guy's pretty good...
Neji!
That's Neji all right!
Not yet...
I won't let you escape that easily!
I won't let you go any further from here!
It's useless.
Well, that's fine.
It seems you're the strongest
out of the lot.
Aw man, now I wanna play...
It's such a waste if
a game isn't played little by little.
For starters,
I'll play and kill you in three minutes.
I got you.
You're pretty good at handling Chakra
and you've got sharp eyes.
You release Chakra from
the Chakra points in your hands
like a sharp needle.
You see the thin part of the thread
with Chakra running through it and attack.
I see, I've heard from Orochimaru-sama...
This is what's called Gentle Fist, isn't it?
But if you can't use
those annoying hands
they can't cut my threads either.
Man, games the instant you know
the rules of engagement
are no longer interesting.
It's only been a minute
but I'm already tired of you.
Die!
Ninja Art:
Gum Style Spider Thread
What?!
How did he...?!
I'll explain specially to you.
It's not just my hands
I can release Chakra from
all of the Chakra points on my body.
And it's game over.
Gentle Fist: 8 trigrams 64 palms!
GET UP aa sumimasen
get up! oh, I'm sorry
goku tama ni boku tama ni
once in a long while, once in a while
yume ni yabureru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person broken by dreams
yama no you ni mieru
kamisama ni hotokesama ni
clinging to God, clinging to Buddha
sugari naiteru hito no kakera ga
the remnants of a person crying
yama no you ni mieru
danran dansu de RANDEBUU
rendezvous with a happy dance circle
ore shouri no poozu da randaran
this is my victory pose, round and around
SHEIKU SHEIKU SHEIKU sagasou janai
shake shake shake let's look
owaranai baibai no RIZUMU de
with a bye-bye rhythm that never ends
yama no you ni mieru
The attack on his Chakra points
is ineffective.
On top of that,
he switched to a long-distance attack
to avoid Gentle Fist.
This guy blocks my every move
and he quickly reads my hands.
This is bad. I'm at a disadvantage
if the fight drags on.
And if he noticed that then...
Next time:
"360 degree Vision: The Byakugan's Blind Spot."